Guide to the Comic book collection, about 1984-2004.
Comic book collection
- Mask: The Mask Strikes Back, 1995; 2 (Box 19)
- Mask: The Mask Strikes Back, 1995; 3 (Box 19)
- Mask: The Mask Strikes Back, 1995; 4 (Box 19)
- Mask: The Mask Strikes Back, 1995; 5 (Box 19)
- Mask: World Tour, 1995; 1 (Box 19)
- Meathaüs, 2000; 2 (Box 19)
  Publisher: Meathaus Press
- Mek, 2001; 1 (Box 19)
  Artist/Penciler: Steve Rolston
- Mek, 2001; 2 (Box 19)
- Mek, 2001; 3 (Box 19)
- Metal Men (v.2), 1993; 1 (Box 19)
  Author: Mike Carlin
  Artist/Penciler: Dan Jurgens
- Metal Men (v.2), 1993; 2 (Box 19)
- Metal Men (v.2), 1993; 3 (Box 19)
- Metal Men (v.2), 1994; 4 (Box 19)
- Metropol A.D. (v.2), 1992; 1 (Box 19)
- Metropol A.D. (v.2), 1992; 2 (Box 19)
- Metropol A.D. (v.2), 1992; 3 (Box 19)
- Michaelangelo, 1985; 1 (Box 19)
  Notes: Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles spin-off. 2 copies.
- Midnight, Mass, 2002; 1 (Box 19)
  Author: John Rozum
  Artist/Penciler: Jesus Saiz
- Midnight, Mass, 2002; 2 (Box 19)
- Midnight, Mass, 2002; 3 (Box 19)
- Midnight, Mass, 2002; 4 (Box 19)
- Midnight, Mass, 2002; 5 (Box 19)
- Midnight, Mass, 2002; 6 (Box 19)
- Midnight, Mass, 2002; 7 (Box 19)
- Midnight, Mass, 2003; 8 (Box 19)
- Midnight, Mass: Here There Be Monsters, 2003; 1 (Box 19)
- Midnight, Mass: Here There Be Monsters, 2003; 2 (Box 19)
- Midnight, Mass: Here There Be Monsters, 2003; 3 (Box 19)
- Midnight, Mass: Here There Be Monsters, 2003; 4 (Box 19)
- Midnight, Mass: Here There Be Monsters, 2003; 5 (Box 19)
- Midnight, Mass: Here There Be Monsters, 2003; 6 (Box 19)
- Milk & Cheese, 1991; 1 (Box 19)
- Milk & Cheese, 1993; 4 (Box 19)
- Milk & Cheese, 1994; 5 (Box 19)
- Millennium Fever, 1995; 1 (Box 19)
  Author: Nick Abadzis
- Millennium Fever, 1995; 2 (Box 19)
- Millennium Fever, 1995; 3 (Box 19)
- Millennium Fever, 1996; 4 (Box 19)
- Ministry of Space, 2001; 2 (Box 19)
- Minx, The, 1998; 1 (Box 19)
- Minx, The, 1998; 2 (Box 19)
- Minx, The, 1998; 3 (Box 19)
- Minx, The, 1999; 4 (Box 19)
- Minx, The, 1999; 5 (Box 19)
- Minx, The, 1999; 6 (Box 19)
- Minx, The, 1999; 7 (Box 19)
- Minx, The, 1999; 8 (Box 19)
- Miracleman, 1990; 17 (Box 19)
- Miracleman, 1990; 18 (Box 19)
- Miracleman, 1990; 19 (Box 19)
- Miracleman, 1991; 20 (Box 19)
- Miracleman, 1991; 21 (Box 19)
- Miracleman, 1991; 22 (Box 19)
- Miracleman, 1991; 23 (Box 19)
- Miracleman: Apocrypha, 1991; 1 (Box 19)
  Notes: three issue miniseries
- Miracleman: Apocrypha, 1992; 2 (Box 19)
  Notes: three issue miniseries; multiple artists and writers featuring Neil Gaiman, Mark Buckingham, Kurt Busiek, and Stephan Petrucha
- Miracleman: Apocrypha, 1992; 3 (Box 19)
  Notes: three issue miniseries; featuring Neil Gaiman, Mark Buckingham, Allan Moore, Alex Ross
- Mister E, 1991; 1 (Box 19)
  Author: K.W. Jeter
- Mister E, 1991; 2 (Box 19)
- Mister E, 1991; 3 (Box 19)
- Mister E, 1991; 4 (Box 19)
- Mister Miracle (v.3), 1996; 1 (Box 19)
  Author: Kevin Dooley
  Artist/Penciler: Steve Crespo
- Mister Miracle (v.3), 1996; 2 (Box 19)
- Mister Miracle (v.3), 1996; 3 (Box 19)
- Mister Miracle (v.3), 1996; 4 (Box 19)
- Mister X (v.3), 1996; 1 (Box 19)
  Author: Deborah Marks
  Artist/Penciler: Gene Gonzales
- Monarchy, 2001; 1 (Box 19)
  Author: Doselle Young
- Monkeyman and O'Brien, 1996; 1 (Box 19)
  Author: Art Adams
- Monkeyman and O'Brien, 1996; 2 (Box 19)
- Monkeyman and O'Brien, 1996; 3 (Box 19)
- Moon Knight, 1998; 1 (Box 19)
- Morningstar Special, 1990; 1 (Box 19)
  Notes: Elementals spin-off
- Moth Special, 2004 (Box 19)
  Author: Gary Martin
  Artist/Penciler: Steve Rude
- Muktuk Wolfsbreath: Hardboiled Shaman, 1998; 1 (Box 19)
- Muktuk Wolfsbreath: Hardboiled Shaman, 1998; 2 (Box 19)
- Muktuk Wolfsbreath: Hardboiled Shaman, 1998; 3 (Box 19)
- My Faith in Frankie, 2004; 1 (Box 19)
  Artist/Penciler: Marc Hempel, Sonny Liew
- My Faith in Frankie, 2004; 2 (Box 19)
- My Faith in Frankie, 2004; 3 (Box 19)
- My Faith in Frankie, 2004; 4 (Box 19)
- Mythos: The Final Tour, 1996; 1 (Box 19)
- Mythos: The Final Tour, 1996; 2 (Box 19)
- Mythos: The Final Tour, 1996; 3 (Box 19)
- Names of Magic, The, 2001; 1 (Box 19)
  Notes: Books of Magic spin-off
- Names of Magic, The, 2001; 2 (Box 19)
- Names of Magic, The, 2001; 3 (Box 19)
- Names of Magic, The, 2001; 4 (Box 19)
- Names of Magic, The, 2001; 5 (Box 19)
- Negative Burn, 1994; 11 (Box 19)
  Notes: multiple artists and writers featuring Alan Moore, Brian Bolland, Neil Gaiman, Phillip Hetser, Matt Feazell, Mark Chiarello
- Negative Burn, 1994; 13 (Box 19)
- Negative Burn, 1994; 44 (Box 19)
- New Defenders, The, 1983; 125 (Box 19)
- New Defenders, The, 1983; 126 (Box 19)
- New Defenders, The, 1984; 127 (Box 19)
  Artist/Penciler: Sal Buscema, Alan Kupperberg
- New Defenders, The, 1984; 128 (Box 19)
- New Defenders, The, 1984; 129 (Box 19)
- New Defenders, The, 1984; 130 (Box 19)
- New Defenders, The, 1984; 131 (Box 19)
- New Defenders, The, 1984; 132 (Box 19)
- New Defenders, The, 1984; 133 (Box 19)
- New Defenders, The, 1984; 134 (Box 19)
- New Defenders, The, 1984; 135 (Box 19)
- New Defenders, The, 1984; 136 (Box 19)
- New Defenders, The, 1984; 137 (Box 19)
- New Defenders, The, 1984; 138 (Box 19)
- New Defenders, The, 1985; 139 (Box 19)
- New Defenders, The, 1985; 140 (Box 19)
- New Defenders, The, 1985; 141 (Box 19)
- New Defenders, The, 1985; 142 (Box 19)
- New Defenders, The, 1985; 143 (Box 19)
- New Defenders, The, 1985; 144 (Box 19)
- New Defenders, The, 1985; 145 (Box 19)
- New Defenders, The, 1985; 146 (Box 19)
- New Defenders, The, 1985; 147 (Box 19)
- New Defenders, The, 1985; 148 (Box 19)
- New Defenders, The, 1985; 149 (Box 19)
- New Defenders, The, 1985; 150 (Box 19)
- New Defenders, The, 1986; 151 (Box 19)
- New Defenders, The, 1986; 152 (Box 19)
- New DNAgents, 1985; 1 (Box 19)
- New DNAgents, 1985; 2 (Box 19)
- New DNAgents, 1985; 3 (Box 19)
- New DNAgents, 1985; 4 (Box 19)
  Artist/Penciler: Chuck Patton
- New DNAgents, 1986; 5 (Box 19)
- New DNAgents, 1986; 6 (Box 19)
- New DNAgents, 1986; 7 (Box 19)
- New DNAgents, 1986; 8 (Box 19)
- New DNAgents, 1986; 9 (Box 19)
- New DNAgents, 1986; 10 (Box 19)
- New DNAgents, 1986; 12 (Box 19)
- New DNAgents, 1986; 13 (Box 19)
- New DNAgents, 1986; 14 (Box 19)
- New Gods (v.4), 1995; 1 (Box 19)
  Artist/Penciler: Rachel Pollack
- New Gods (v.4), 1995; 2 (Box 19)
- New Gods (v.4), 1995; 3 (Box 19)
- New Gods (v.4), 1996; 4 (Box 19)
- New Gods (v.4), 1996; 12 (Box 19)
  Notes: 1996 relaunch
- New Gods (v.4), 1996; 13 (Box 19)
- New Gods (v.4), 1996; 14 (Box 19)
- New Gods (v.4), 1996; 15 (Box 19)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1983; 1 (Box 20)
  Artist/Penciler: Bob McLeod
- New Mutants (v.1), 1983; 2 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1983; 3 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1983; 4 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1983; 5 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1983; 6 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1983; 7 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1983; 8 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1983; 9 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1983; 10 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1984; 11 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1984; 12 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1984; 13 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1984; 14 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1984; 15 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1984; 16 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1984; 17 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1984; 18 (Box 20)
  Artist/Penciler: Bill Sienkiewicz
- New Mutants (v.1), 1984; 19 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1984; 20 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1984; 21 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1984; 22 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1985; 23 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1985; 24 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1985; 25 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1985; 26 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1985; 27 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1985; 28 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1985; 29 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1985; 30 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1985; 31 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1985; 32 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1985; 33 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1985; 34 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1986; 35 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1986; 36 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1986; 37 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1986; 38 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1986; 39 (Box 20)
  Artist/Penciler: Keith Pollard
- New Mutants (v.1), 1986; 40 (Box 20)
  Artist/Penciler: Jackson Guice
- New Mutants (v.1), 1986; 41 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1986; 43 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1986; 44 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1986; 45 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1986; 46 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1986; 47 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1987; 48 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1987; 49 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1987; 50 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1987; 51 (Box 20)
  Artist/Penciler: Kevin Nowlan
- New Mutants (v.1), 1987; 52 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1987; 53 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1987; 54 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1987; 55 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1987; 56 (Box 20)
  Artist/Penciler: June Brigman
- New Mutants (v.1), 1987; 57 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1987; 58 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1987; 59 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1988; 60 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1988; 61 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1988; 62 (Box 20)
  Artist/Penciler: John Muth
- New Mutants (v.1), 1988; 63 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1988; 64 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1988; 65 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1988; 66 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1988; 67 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1988; 68 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1988; 69 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1988; 70 (Box 20)
  Artist/Penciler: Terry Shoemaker
- New Mutants (v.1), 1988; 71 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1989; 72 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1989; 73 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1989; 74 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1989; 75 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1989; 76 (Box 20)
  Artist/Penciler: Rich Buckler
- New Mutants (v.1), 1989; 77 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1989; 78 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1989; 79 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1989; 80 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1989; 81 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1989; 82 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1989; 83 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1990; 84 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1990; 95 (Box 20)
  Artist/Penciler: Rob Liefeld
- New Mutants (v.1), 1990; 96 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1990; 97 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1990; 98 (Box 20)
  Author: Fabian Nicieza
- New Mutants (v.1), 1990; 99 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1990; 100 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1983; Ann. 1 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1984; Ann. 2 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1985; Ann. 3 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1986; Ann. 4 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1987; Ann. 5 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.1), 1989; Ann. 7 (Box 20)
  Artist/Penciler: Guang Yap
- New Mutants (v.1) Special Edition, 1985 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.2), 2003; 1 (Box 20)
  Author: Nunzio DeFilippis, Christina Weir
  Artist/Penciler: Keron Grant
- New Mutants (v.2), 2003; 2 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.2), 2003; 3 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.2), 2003; 4 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.2), 2003; 5 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.2), 2003; 6 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.2), 2004; 7 (Box 20)
  Artist/Penciler: Carlo Barberi
- New Mutants (v.2), 2004; 8 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.2), 2004; 9 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.2), 2004; 10 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.2), 2004; 11 (Box 20)
- New Mutants (v.2), 2004; 12 (Box 20)
  Artist/Penciler: Khari Randolph
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1981; 5 (Box 20)
  Artist/Penciler: Curt Swan
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1981; 6 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1981; 7 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1981; 8 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1981; 9 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1981; 10 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1981; 11 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1981; 12 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1981; 13 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1981; 14 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1982; 15 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1982; 16 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1982; 17 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1982; 18 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1982; 19 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1982; 20 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1982; 21 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1982; 22 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1982; 23 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1982; 24 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1982; 25 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1982; 26 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1983; 27 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1983; 28 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1983; 29 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1983; 30 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1983; 31 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1983; 32 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1983; 33 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1983; 34 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1983; 35 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1983; 36 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1983; 37 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1983; 38 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1984; 39 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1984; 40 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1982; Ann. 1 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.1), 1983; Ann. 2 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1984; 1 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1984; 2 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1984; 3 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1984; 4 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1984; 5 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1985; 6 (Box 20)
  Artist/Penciler: Romeo Tanghal
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1985; 7 (Box 20)
  Artist/Penciler: Jose Louis Garcia Lopez
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1985; 8 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1985; 9 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1985; 10 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1985; 11 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1985; 12 (Box 20)
  Artist/Penciler: Stan Woch
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1985; 13 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1985; 14 (Box 20)
  Artist/Penciler: Eduardo Barreto
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1985; 15 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1985; 16 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1985; 17 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1986; 18 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1986; 19 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1986; 20 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1986; 21 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1986; 22 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1986; 23 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1986; 24 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1986; 25 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1986; 26 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1986; 27 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1986; 28 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1986; 29 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1987; 30 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1987; 31 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1987; 32 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1985; Ann. 1 (Box 20)
- New Teen Titans (v.2), 1986; Ann. 2 (Box 20)
  Notes: Continues as New Titans
- New Titans, 1988; 51 (Box 20)
  Notes: Continues from New Teen Titans (v.2)
- New Titans, 1992; 89 (Box 20)
- New Titans, 1993; 94 (Box 20)
- New Titans, 1993; 97 (Box 20)
- New Titans, 1993; 100 (Box 20)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2001; 114 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2001; 115 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2001; 116 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2001; 117 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2001; 118 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2001; 119 (Box 21)
  Artist/Penciler: Igor Kordey
- New X-Men (v.1), 2002; 120 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2002; 121 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2002; 122 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2002; 123 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2002; 124 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2002; 125 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2002; 126 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2002; 127 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2002; 128 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2002; 129 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2002; 130 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2002; 131 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2003; 132 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2003; 133 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2003; 134 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2003; 135 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2003; 136 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2003; 137 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2003; 138 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2003; 139 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2003; 140 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2003; 141 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2003; 142 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2003; 143 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2004; 144 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2004; 145 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2004; 146 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2004; 147 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2004; 148 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2004; 149 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2004; 150 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2004; 151 (Box 21)
  Artist/Penciler: Mark Silvestri
- New X-Men (v.1), 2004; 153 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2004; 154 (Box 21)
- New X-Men (v.1), 2004; 155 (Box 21)
  Artist/Penciler: Salvador Larroca
- New X-Men (v.1), 2001; Ann. 2001 (Box 21)
  Artist/Penciler: Leinil Francis Yu
- New X-Men (v.2), 2004; 1 (Box 21)
  Notes: Alt. Title: New X-Men: Academy X
- New Year's Evil: Gog, 1998; 1 (Box 21)
  Artist/Penciler: Jerry Ordway
- New Year's Evil: Prometheus, 1998; 1 (Box 21)
- New Year's Evil: Scarecrow, 1998; 1 (Box 21)
- Nexus Meets Madman Special, 1996 (Box 21)
- Nexus The Liberator, 1992; 1 (Box 21)
  Artist/Penciler: John Calimee
- Nexus The Liberator, 1992; 2 (Box 21)
- Nexus The Liberator, 1992; 3 (Box 21)
- Nexus The Liberator, 1992; 4 (Box 21)
- Nexus: Alien Justice, 1992; 1 (Box 21)
  Author: Mike Baron
  Notes: iternally #82
- Nexus: Alien Justice, 1993; 2 (Box 21)
  Notes: internally #83
- Nexus: Alien Justice, 1993; 3 (Box 21)
  Notes: internally #84
- Nexus: Executioner's Song, 1996; 1 (Box 21)
  Notes: internally #89
- Nexus: Executioner's Song, 1996; 2 (Box 21)
  Notes: internally #90
- Nexus: Executioner's Song, 1996; 3 (Box 21)
  Notes: internally #91
- Nexus: Executioner's Song, 1996; 4 (Box 21)
  Notes: internally #92
- Nexus: God Con, 1997; 1 (Box 21)
  Notes: internally #93
- Nexus: God Con, 1997; 2 (Box 21)
  Notes: internally #94
- Nexus: Nightmare in Blue, 1995; 1 (Box 21)
  Notes: internally #95
- Nexus: Nightmare in Blue, 1995; 2 (Box 21)
  Notes: internally #96
- Nexus: Nightmare in Blue, 1995; 3 (Box 21)
  Notes: internally #97
- Nexus: Nightmare in Blue, 1995; 4 (Box 21)
  Notes: internally #98
- Nexus: The Origin, 1992; — (Box 21)
  Notes: internally #81
- Nexus: Wages of Sin, 1995; 1 (Box 21)
  Notes: internally #85
- Nexus: Wages of Sin, 1995; 2 (Box 21)
  Notes: internally #86
- Nexus: Wages of Sin, 1995; 3 (Box 21)
  Notes: internally #87
- Nexus: Wages of Sin, 1995; 4 (Box 21)
  Notes: internally #88
- Night Force (v.2), 1996; 1 (Box 21)
- Nightcrawler (v.1), 1985; 1 (Box 21)
- Nightcrawler (v.1), 1985; 2 (Box 21)
- Nightcrawler (v.1), 1985; 3 (Box 21)
- Nightcrawler (v.1), 1985; 4 (Box 21)
- Nocturnals, 1995; 2 (Box 21)
  Author: Dan Brereton
  Artist/Penciler: Dan Brereton
  Publisher: Malibu/Bravura
  Notes: Alt. Title: Nocturnals: Black Planet. 1st miniseries
- Nocturnals, 1995; 3 (Box 21)
- Nocturnals, 1995; 4 (Box 21)
- Nocturnals, 1995; 6 (Box 21)
- Nocturnals: The Dark Forever, 2001; 1 (Box 21)
- Nocturnals: The Dark Forever, 2001; 2 (Box 21)
- Nocturnals: The Dark Forever, 2001; 3 (Box 21)
- Nocturnals: Troll Bridge, 2000 (Box 21)
- Nocturnals: Witching Hour, 1997 (Box 21)
- Ocean, 2004; 1 (Box 21)
- Ocean, 2004; 2 (Box 21)
- Ocean, 2004; 3 (Box 21)
- Ocean, 2004; 4 (Box 21)
- Official Handbook of the Marvel Universe, 1983; 1 (Box 21)
  Notes: 12 issue miniseries
- Official Handbook of the Marvel Universe, 1983; 2 (Box 21)
- Official Handbook of the Marvel Universe, 1983; 3 (Box 21)
- Official Handbook of the Marvel Universe, 1983; 4 (Box 21)
- Official Handbook of the Marvel Universe, 1983; 5 (Box 21)
- Official Handbook of the Marvel Universe, 1983; 6 (Box 21)
- Official Handbook of the Marvel Universe, 1983; 7 (Box 21)
- Official Handbook of the Marvel Universe, 1983; 8 (Box 21)
- Official Handbook of the Marvel Universe, 1983; 9 (Box 21)
- Official Handbook of the Marvel Universe, 1983; 10 (Box 21)
- Official Handbook of the Marvel Universe, 1983; 11 (Box 21)
- Official Handbook of the Marvel Universe, 1983; 12 (Box 21)
- Official Handbook of the Marvel Universe, 1984; 13 (Box 21)
- Official Handbook of the Marvel Universe, 1984; 14 (Box 21)
- Official Handbook of the Marvel Universe, 1984; 15 (Box 21)
- Official Handbook of the Marvel Universe: Deluxe Edition, 1985; 1 (Box 21)
- Official Handbook of the Marvel Universe: Deluxe Edition, 1985; 2 (Box 21)
- Official Handbook of the Marvel Universe: Deluxe Edition, 1985; 5 (Box 21)
- Official Handbook of the Marvel Universe: Deluxe Edition, 1985; 6 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1983; 1 (Box 21)
  Author: Roger Slifer
- Omega Men (v.1), 1983; 2 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1983; 3 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1983; 4 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1983; 5 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1983; 6 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1983; 7 (Box 21)
  Artist/Penciler: Tod Smith
- Omega Men (v.1), 1983; 8 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1983; 9 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1984; 10 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1984; 11 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1984; 12 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1984; 13 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1984; 14 (Box 21)
  Author: Todd Klein
- Omega Men (v.1), 1984; 15 (Box 21)
  Author: Joe Cavalieri
  Artist/Penciler: Alex Nino
- Omega Men (v.1), 1984; 16 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1984; 17 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1984; 18 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1984; 19 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1984; 20 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1984; 21 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1985; 22 (Box 21)
  Author: Sharman Divono
- Omega Men (v.1), 1985; 23 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1985; 24 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1985; 25 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1985; 26 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1985; 27 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1985; 28 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1985; 29 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1985; 30 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1985; 31 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1985; 32 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1985; 33 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1986; 34 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1986; 35 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1986; 36 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1986; 37 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1986; 38 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1984; Ann. 1 (Box 21)
- Omega Men (v.1), 1985; Ann. 2 (Box 21)
- Only the End of the World Again, 2000 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.1), 1985; 1 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.1), 1985; 2 (Box 21)
  Artist/Penciler: Todd McFarlane
- Outsiders, The (v.1), 1986; 3 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.1), 1986; 4 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.1), 1986; 5 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.1), 1986; 6 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.1), 1986; 7 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.1), 1986; 8 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.1), 1986; 9 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.1), 1986; 10 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.1), 1986; 11 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.1), 1986; 12 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.1), 1986; 13 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.1), 1986; 14 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.1), 1987; 15 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.1), 1987; 16 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.1), 1987; 17 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.1), 1987; 18 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.1), 1987; 19 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.1), 1987; 20 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.1), 1987; 21 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.1) Special, 1987; 1 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.3), 2003; 1 (Box 21)
  Artist/Penciler: Tom Raney
- Outsiders, The (v.3), 2003; 2 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.3), 2003; 3 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.3), 2003; 4 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.3), 2003; 5 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.3), 2004; 6 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.3), 2004; 7 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.3), 2004; 8 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.3), 2004; 9 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.3), 2004; 10 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.3), 2004; 11 (Box 21)
  Artist/Penciler: Will Conrad
- Outsiders, The (v.3), 2004; 12 (Box 21)
  Artist/Penciler: Tom Derenick
- Outsiders, The (v.3), 2004; 13 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.3), 2004; 14 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.3), 2004; 15 (Box 21)
- Outsiders, The (v.3), 2004; 16 (Box 21)
- Oz Squad, 1995; 5 (Box 21)
  Author: Steven Ahlquist
  Artist/Penciler: Terry Loh
  Publisher: Patchwork Press
- Phoenix: The Untold Story, 1983; 1 (Box 21)
- Planetary, 1999; 2 (Box 22)
- Planetary, 1999; 3 (Box 22)
- Planetary, 1999; 6 (Box 22)
- Planetary, 1999; 7 (Box 22)
- Planetary, 1999; 8 (Box 22)